okay here we're going to find
25% of the number 76 whenever you're
finding a percentage of a number you can
read of basically just replace it with
multiplication and the only thing we
need to do is we need to turn 25% either
into a
decimal or a fraction before we
multiply so that's what I'm going to do
well 25% uh we can write that 25 over
100 of is going to be our
multiplication of 76 I'm even going to
write that as 76 over 1 and now we can
just start simplifying so 25 over 100
that would actually reduce to 1 over4 if
we divide top and bottom by
25 so multiplied by 76 over
1 well that's just going to give us 76
over
four and four will go into 76
evenly four will go into seven once 1 *
4 is
four drop down subtract we'll get our
three and drop down our six and then
four will go into 36 19 times so 76 / 4
is 19
so if you had
25% of say $76
you would have exactly $19